{"questions":[
        {"questiontext":"A user provides a login name to profess and identity.  What is this called?",
        "answerchoice1":"Authentication",
        "answerchoice2":"Accountability",
        "answerchoice3":"Identification",
        "answerchoice4":"Accounting",
        "answer":3},

    {"questiontext":"What must occur before a system can implement access controls?",
        "answerchoice1":"Identification and authentication",
        "answerchoice2":"Identification and accountability",
        "answerchoice3":"Authentication and accounting",
        "answerchoice4":"Accountability and availability",
        "answer":1},

    {"questiontext":"Which of the following methods are used for authentication?",
        "answerchoice1":"Say, think, are",
        "answerchoice2":"Know, have, type",
        "answerchoice3":"Know, say, are",
        "answerchoice4":"Know, have, are",
        "answer":4},

    {"questiontext":"Password policy.  What is the recommended minimum time that can elapse before a password should be changed?",
        "answerchoice1":"Changed before at least one day has elapsed",
        "answerchoice2":"Changed before at least five days have elapsed",
        "answerchoice3":"Changed at least every 90 days",
        "answerchoice4":"Changed at least every 120 days",
        "answer":3},

    {"questiontext":"Which does NOT ensure that a password is strong?",
        "answerchoice1":"Sufficient length",
        "answerchoice2":"Changed frequently",
        "answerchoice3":"Mixture of different character types",
        "answerchoice4":"Does not include any part of the user's name",
        "answer":2},

    {"questiontext":"Which is not used for biometrics?",
        "answerchoice1":"Retinal scans",
        "answerchoice2":"Voice recognition",
        "answerchoice3":"Pattern recognition",
        "answerchoice4":"Fingerprints",
        "answer":3},

    {"questiontext":"Consideration for biometric accuracy?",
        "answerchoice":"1FRF",
        "answerchoice":"FAER",
        "answerchoice":"CER",
        "answerchoice":"CEFR",
        "answer":3},

    {"questiontext":"What is not used for SSO?",
        "answerchoice1":"Kerberos",
        "answerchoice2":"Decentralized authentication",
        "answerchoice3":"KryptoKnight",
        "answerchoice4":"SASAME",
        "answer":2},

    {"questiontext":"What allows users to access multiple systems, managed by different orgs, after logging on only once?",
        "answerchoice1":"Clark-Wilson",
        "answerchoice2":"Chinese Wall",
        "answerchoice3":"Federated access",
        "answerchoice4":"SaaS",
        "answer":3},

    {"questiontext":"Which is true for a one-time password?",
        "answerchoice1":"Hardware tokens are asynch",
        "answerchoice2":"OPIE uses AES to encrypt the password",
        "answerchoice3":"Bell-LaPadula uses synch onetime passwords",
        "answerchoice4":"S/KEY uses MD4 or MD5 to create a hash",
        "answer":4},

    {"questiontext":"What enforces logical access controls?",
        "answerchoice1":"Security kernel",
        "answerchoice2":"Security guards",
        "answerchoice3":"Alarm systems",
        "answerchoice4":"Cipher locks",
        "answer":1},

    {"qustiontext":"Which is NOT an example of tech that uses onetime passwords?",
        "answerchoice1":"S/Key",
        "answerchoice2":"OPIE",
        "answerchoice3":"Biometrics",
        "answerchoice4":"Harware-based token",
        "answer":3},

    {"questiontext":"Enforces separation of duties?",
        "answerchoice1":"Chinese Wall and Clark-Wilson",
        "answerchoice2":"Chinese Wall and Biba",
        "answerchoice3":"Clark-Wilson and Bell-LaPadula",
        "answerchoice4":"Biba and Bell-LaPadula",
        "answer":1},

    {"questontext":"What is RBAC?",
        "answerchoice1":"Role-based access control",
        "answerchoice2":"Risk-based access control",
        "answerchoice3":"Risk buffer acceptance containment",
        "answerchoice4":"Role-based accountability computer",
        "answer":1},

    {"questiontext":"What prevents a user form reusing the same password?",
        "answerchoice1":"Minimum password age",
        "answerchoice2":"Max password age",
        "answerchoice3":"Password length",
        "answerchoice4":"Password history",
        "answer":4},

    {"questiontext":"User leaves company. Immediately:",
        "answerchoice1":"Delete users account",
        "answerchoice2":"Disable user's account",
        "answerchoice3":"Change user's password",
        "answerchoice4":"Change the user's permission",
        "answer":2},

    {"questiontext":"Which is SaaS?",
        "answerchoice1":"Access to O/S over the internet",
        "answerchoice2":"Access to server over the internet",
        "answerchoice3":"Web-based email",
        "answerchoice4":"VM escape",
        "answer":3},

    {"questiontext":"What is the greatest risk to virtual systems?",
        "answerchoice1":"Confidentiality",
        "answerchoice2":"VM escape",
        "answerchoice3":"Increase power and cooling costs",
        "answerchoice4":"Loss of control of data in cloud",
        "answer":2}
 ]
}
